<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CNVTeachers</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="server_failed_title">Network Failed</string>
    <string name="server_failed_msg">Internet problem or server network error. Please try after some time later or update your application. \n\nContact us on support@cloudnxtvision.com </string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="string_help_text"> The permission is missing.\n\nTo grant this permission click on Settings, then Permissions and turn the permission on.\n\nThen click back twice to return to the app</string>
    <string name="quit">Exit App</string>
    <string name="unable_to_fetch">Unable to fetch the require data right now. please check your internet connection and try after some times later.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field">Please enter atleast Name or Admission No. value to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field0">Please enter  Name or Admission No.  and From Date and To date value to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field2">Please select Class and Division  to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field5">Please select Class to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field1">Please select Class , Division , FromDate , ToDate to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field3">Please select FromDate , ToDate to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field4">Please enter atleast Name or Admission No. or Class and division value to find correct result.</string>
    <string name="error_input_field6">Please select Academic Year and Admission Year and Class and Division and Exam name value to find correct result.</string>

    <string name="error_server_down">Internet unavailable or the server is down, This may take a while. Please try again some times later.</string>
    <string name="company_addr">Designed and developed by Cloud Next Vision Systems. Copyright © 2017 All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="NoStud">No students are assigned for this project.</string>
    <string name="error_input">Please enter Project Aim, Title, Description and Select Class,Division,From date, To date to find the correct result. </string>
</resources>
